Mayank Chaturvedi

Summary_

I am a computer science undergraduate with experience in the field of Artificial Intelligence, Algorithmic Optimizations and Web Development. Being an active competitive programmer, solving interesting problems has always delighted me. I enjoy learning new IT technologies and implementing them. My habit of interacting with new people and exploring newer ideas allows me to never stop experimenting. It also helps me develop a good communication skill.

Work Experience _____

Centre for Railway Information Systems

New Delhi, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

May. 2019 - July. 2019

· To be updated

Freelancer

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE/WEB DEVELOPMENT

May. 2020 - Present

- · Developed various image recognition models using Python, PyTorch and fastai achieving some state of the art outcomes
- Built and deployed the overall service infrastructures utilizing flask and various web services

Education

Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani KK Birla, Goa Campus

Goa, India

B.E. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Graduating 2022

Doing major in Computer Science as well as in Mathematics. Overall: 8.5 CGPA

Honors & Awards

INTERNATIONAL

2020	Global Rank 143, Google Kick Start Round D	Google
2020	Global Rank 26, Codeforces Round 641; handle mac	Codeforces
2019	Global Rank 63, November Cook-Off, Div1; handle mac1309	Codechef

DOMESTIC

2019	21st Rank, ICPC India Kanpur Regional Final,19	ICPC
2019	Ranked 13, TCO India Finals, Jaipur	TopCoder
2019	Course Topper, Number Theory	BITS Pilani, Goa

Writing.

A Bit of Mac Blog

FOUNDER & WRITER June. 2020 - PRESENT

• A blog on Travelling, Artificial Intelligence, Psychology and Mathematics

Extracurricular Activity _____

AlgomaniaX (Competitive Coder' Network of BITS Goa)

Goa India

PRESIDENT AT 2019

August. 2019 - Present

- Reformed the hierarchy of the club
- Conducted various events with collaboration with big coding platforms of US and India

JULY 13, 2020 MAYANK CHATURVEDI · RÉSUMÉ